v9seo.com 2015-09-29

# Privacy Policy | Volume Nine SEO

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Volume Nine collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.v9seo.com and http://eduki.com websites (“Sites”). This privacy policy applies to the Sites and all products and services offered by Volume Nine.

The Sites are owned and operated by Volume Nine. The Sites are offered subject to your acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies (including, without limitation, Volume Nine’s Privacy Policy) and procedures that may be published from time to time on this Site by Volume Nine (collectively, the “Agreement”). ****

Please read this Agreement carefully before accessing or using the Sites. By accessing or using any part of the websites, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this agreement. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the Sites or use any services. If these terms and conditions are considered an offer by Volume Nine, acceptance is expressly limited to these terms.

**What information do we collect?**

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Sites. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Sites. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Sites, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. ****

What do we use your information for?

Volume Nine, collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize user experience.We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site.We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service.Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into database, accessible only by those authorized with special access rights, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we use cookies (which are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer’s hard drive) to help us understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Third party links**

Our site may contain links to third party sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except to provide products or services you’ve requested. Non-personally identifiable information may be released to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, and/or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

**Intellectual property**

This Agreement does not transfer from Volume Nine to you any Volume Nine or third party intellectual property, and all right, title and interest in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Volume Nine. Volume Nine logo, and all other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with Volume Nine, or the Site are trademarks or registered trademarks of Volume Nine or Volume Nine licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Site may be the trademarks of other third parties. Your use of the Site grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any Volume Nine or third-party trademarks.

**Changes**

Volume Nine reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Agreement. It is your responsibility to check this Agreement periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the Site following the posting of any changes to this Agreement constitutes acceptance of those changes. Volume Nine may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Site (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new features and/or services shall be subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
